Catch catch catch this man should save himself,
catch catch catch catch, don't let him go, what has happened today,
I have not eaten, you have just
eaten,
hey fat man listen, the police is after me, run after me, I will
give you ₹10,
₹10,000, come on come on brother, run after me, I will
talk about the setting later, hey
find him where has he gone, yes brother, have
you seen this man running away from here,
no sir, I have never seen this man.
Seat friend, if you don't see it anywhere then
inform Pilibhit police station.  There
is a reward of ₹50,000 for the person who gives its address.
₹00 reward
catch it [laughs].  Come, take him to the police station.   Let's
go to the police station.  Sir, how will I get those ₹50,000
?  Come to the police station in the evening.